As usual...
I've come to Toyohashi station to take photos
for the Literature Club homepage.
I heard Komari was at a library in town, but...
Oh, there she is.
She's looking something up...
Hey, Koma-
No, wait a sec...
Nyah!
Hmm, I took a good photo.
Nnnn... what are you doing all of a sudden?
Ah, its a photo for the Literature Club homepage.
I wanted authentic shots of club members
and the sights of the city.
Nnn... Nukumizu...
Sit over there.
Eh
Uh... what's wrong?
Nyaa!
Why are you sitting next to me?!
D-Don't move my bag!
This table is big, so it's hard
to talk if we're sitting across from each other, right?
Even if whispering isn't banned,
we shouldn't go over board.
I-Is that so.
That doesn't sound like something
someone who takes creepshots would say.
Someone who takes creepshots?
Here?
We should call the police.
I... I guess someone from the
Literature Club is going to prison.
Eh
That 'someone who takes creepshots'...
...isn't me, is it?
I-it is.
Die.
You've got it all wrong.
In fact, you could call it slander.
I-i-is that all you have to say?
Just listen.
The moment I took the photo,
you noticed me and turned around, right?
In other words,
you were conscious of my presence...
...which doesn't fit the definition of creepshot, right?
No it doesn't!
It's just like a normal shot from the front.
T-taking a photo without consent is a creepshot.
I-I won't accept objections.
Then consent right here.
Look!
It's a good picture, right?
Uh... uh... uhm...
My... face is there.
Ah, you look good in this photo, right?
We need the whole world to see this homepage
so we can spread this charm.
Nyaa!
Uhh... uhmm... ch-charm?
It won't be embarrassing no matter
what part of this library we show...
We need everyone to know that
there's this sort of place in our hometown.
Th-the library?
The library.
But we didn't use the filter
so we probably can't use it...
Alright, let's delete that photo
and take one more.
D-die!
Why?
We can add the filter later.
Show me your phone.
Oh, really?
I-if we mess with the settings menu a bit...
Nnn! Nukumizu! Too close!
Huh, it can't be helped, right?
My phone has a privacy filter.
The both of us can't see
if we don't this.
N-no one wants to see your phone.
My, my...
You don't get it do you?
Eh?
Listen, when I'm on a train...
...and playing one of those social games.
I can't let the
kid sitting next to me see it, right?
Here, this game...
Why not try playing it?
Y-you... haven't died enough?
Ehh... Why do you want me to die so much?
E-enough with that!
If you're done, just be quiet!
You're in the way of my work.
Oh, what have you been looking up?
Re-research for my story.
I'm writing a story about a young villainess...
so I'm researching attire... and buildings...
Hmm... you're actually looking
things up before writing.
Y-you don't?
I do though...
Y-your research is just reading comics
and playing games, isn't it?
How'd you know?
I could tell by reading your stories.
Y-you didn't do any research, so the
descriptions are awkward
and you don't understand women at all.
Oh... If you're going to say that,
then why not teach me?
Ehh... t-teach you what?
If you're going to say I don't understand...
...then teach me.
I have loads of time.
Nyaa!
Uh... uhm...
I-if you don't get women-
Huh? What are you talking about?
Since we're at the library...
...I was thinking you could teach me how to do research.
-ie.
Eh?
D-die!
This is the second time, so die twice!
What "second time?"
What now? Why are you suddenly standing up?
C-come with me...I-I'll teach you
how to use the library.
Hey!
Wait!
Uh... uhm...
Books in the library are divided into
different categories based on certain rules.
L-look.
There's a sticker next to the books
with a number written on it.
This?
For me, even if I know the categories,
I wouldn't know where to start.
I-it's the opposite!
S-someone like you who doesn't know anything should
find out what he needs to know based on the categories.
Uh...
In other words?
F-for example, what's the theme
of the story you're writing?
The main themes are whether the redevelopment of
historic towns is justified and the spirit of regional connections.
Uhh... was that erotic rom-com really that profound?
What I'm writing is a wholesome rom-com.
Uhh... In other words,
I should cut down on sexy descriptions?
N-no... You can... keep those.
Anyway... If you're writing about redevelopment...
Category #671 should have info
on trade policy and governance.
If you have a model town in mind,
how about looking at through regional data at section #09?
J-just looking at the titles is fine.
I see... so a new perspective might
give me a hint on what I should be searching for.
Even if you can't use the info directly,
they'll help with writing descriptions.
Y-your story is set
in a shopping district, right?
The books on commerce and business
from #673 will probably be helpful.
Huh, I didn't even think about that.
In fact, I didn't even know how to use the library.
Shouldn't they have taught this in school?
Th-they did.
Ah
They did?
But if you think about it, not remembering means that knowledge has subconsciously become a part of me.
In a way, the class' goal was met, don't you think?
Nn... what's wrong, Komari?
R-recently... Y-you've started acting like Yanami.
Ah...
Seriously?
D-do some self-reflection.
I will.
This is scary...
The longer I'm close to Yanami,
the more she'll rub off on me...
I have to be careful.
Uhm...
To get back on topic...
We could also ask the librarian for help, right?
Th-that's only the... last resort.
Why?
Having someone you don't know
come up and talk to you...
Impossible...
That's just you, right?
The librarian won't be bothered
whether you know or don't know...
No, they might...
Ri-right?
If we go to extremes, people who aren't
family are all outsiders, right?
Up till today, I might have been too
trusting of others...
I-it's fine if you get it.
D-don't trust them!
It kind of got a little scary.
Is this really okay?
For us to use this sort of stylish library?
If one of the staff talks to us,
an alarm won't go off, right?
D-don't worry, borrowing and returning
are self check out.
We can do it without talking t-to anyone.
Then I guess we don't need to worry.
I guess, we've become library masters, huh?
Th-there's... one more thing... you know.
'One more thing'?
Y-you can reserve seats at this library.
Nu-Nukumizu, have you tried it before?
Not at all. How about you?
N-no...
Like...
I was thinking, "Can't I just use it normally?"
...kind off.
I get it...
I get cold feet thinking that
someone else might need the seat more...
B-but... today is d-different.
L-let's go for it and r-reserve a s-seat!
Are we doing it?
Right here and now?
Uh... uhm...
The booth and lounge seats are...
...unavailable.
How about a counter seat?
The ones that are lined up.
Sitting next to a stranger is...
...scary.
You're right, they're probably enemies.
Ah
There's a box seat open.
The one that's like a bench.
O-oh...
Let's go there.
Umm...
Here, right?
Komari, you can sit by the window.
Ehh
We're sitting together?
This is for two people, right?
And it's the only place that's free.
I-it... is, isn't it.
Komari, You sure you don't want
to continue your research?
I-I'll continue it later at home.
Nukumizu, why are you looking at your phone?
Oh, I was thinking I'd check the home page's photos.
We need to decide which to use.
Eh
It isn't just the photo you took earlier?
Yanami-san made me take her photos too.
Look, they turned out quite alright,
even if I do say so myself.
The aquatic building?
Y-Yanami is eating like always.
Yeah, she really did.
As if it was all just being sucked in...
Th-there are a lot of photos of Yanami, huh.
All the photos of her eating were kind of blurry...
...so I had to retake them again and again.
Before I knew it, she'd eaten all the Canelé.
It was actually an ordeal.
And a waste of memory.
In comparison...
I have one photo...
Yes, thanks to my skill.
J-just one...
What's wrong?
I-isn't my photo a little... blurry?
L-look... over here.
It's on purpose.
On the contrary, it makes the photo more stylish.
Nnn... Uhm...
Over here...
I think there's something
that kind of looks like a face...
Huh? Where?!
Is it this?
You're right, there's an ominous aura.
Ah! Th-that's my leg!
Don't zoom in!
Oh, that wasn't it?
Wait a sec...
Komari, recently...
...hasn't your skirt gotten a little shorter?
Ow!
Why'd you kick me?
Y-your whole body ?????
Huh? What a bizarre insult.
Do you really not like this photo?
Th-that's not the problem...
Uh.... uhm...
Is something wrong? If there is, you can tell me.
I-it's just!
You can...
...take a few more photos...
Huh, what's this?
Komari is getting really fidgety...
It's a little cute, but...
...did something happen?
Ah...
I don't really get it, but...
We should be fine with this one photo.
You're not good with photos, right?
N-no...
Uhm...
I...
If you really don't like this photo, I could blur it?
In fact, if there's a specific part tha-
G-get eaten by fishes!...
...and ride a chikuwa!
Ah! Hey!
Where are you going?
Komari forcibly stood up from her seat and hurriedly left the place.
I wonder what part of this she didn't like?
I think she looks cute in this photo, though...