Today, I'm out shopping with Kaju at the Toyohashi Station building, Kalmia.
It's one of those rare family outings.
Kaju, what are we shopping for today?
We're here to look for clothes.
What kind of outfits do you like, Onii-sama?
Hmm, I don't have a particular preference, but if I had to choose, I guess I like skirts more.
Skirts?
I think you could pull it off, Onii-sama.
Yes, Kaju thinks you would look good in it!
What are you talking about?
Aren't we talking about Kaju's clothes?
Today, we're here to look for clothes for you.
You've made some new friends recently, and you've been going out more often, haven't you?
It's about time you swapped out those clothes from middle school.
I just bought some new ones recently!
You know, the ones with those stylish patterns.
Onii-sama, from now on, dragon patterns are banned in the Nukumizu household.
Isn't that a bit strict?
Nope. It's banned.
Um,
How about the brick-patterned shirt I bought the other day?
Wasn't it cool?
Let's stop casually buying clothes that no one in the world could possibly pull off, okay?
Why not start with something plain first?
I think having a pattern makes it more stylish.
Remember that apron we made in home economics class? The dragon design on it was really cool.
I sealed the dragon away in my elementary school toolbox.
It won't appear for the next 100 years.
Come to think of it, my toolbox also had a dragon pattern.
Alright, let's embark on an adventure from level 1 together!
I see, so we just need to level up and break the dragon's seal.
Are you done trying to defeat Kaju, Onii-sama?
Why is Kaju so strict when it comes to my fashion choices?
You found some nice clothes, didn't you?
I'm not really sure, but is this okay?
I don't think it's that different from the clothes I already have.
It's good to have clothes without zippers or pockets on the sleeves too.
Unbranded...
Unbranded clothes solve everything.
Is that how it is?
So obviously, no anime character T-shirts, right?
Actually, that's totally acceptable.
When going to events or visiting places featured in anime.
Wearing it to an anime shop is actually more like following the dress code.
It's what you would call TPO.
Oh, really?
Actually, the wristband I'm wearing is official merchandise from the currently airing "Absolute Territory Calvados."
So, does that mean it's okay to head to the anime shop downstairs now?
The wristband aside, the anime shop is definitely okay!
Got it.
Is the wristband a no-go?
It's a go from a TPO perspective.
Let's take it off when you're on a date with someone other than Kaju.
Wait, was today a date?
It was.
Was it?
Uh, the entrance is this way...
Huh?
Oh... it's Nukumizu-kun!
Oh, Imouto-chan is with you too.
Yanami-san, it's been a while.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Okay, both of you, line up behind me.
Standing there is in the way, you know.
Huh?
This way, Onii-sama.
Oh...
Um, Yanami-san?
What's this line for?
Today, I was having lunch with a friend.
That's lovely.
Am I being ignored here?
Um, this line...
I was planning to go shopping after having lunch.
I was, but...
Sigh...
My friend got a message from her boyfriend.
She said something urgent came up, and apologized.
Oh, really?
So, what's this line for?
I won't say something silly like "prioritize your friends."
But you know, there should be something more, right?
That girl said she met her boyfriend's mom the other day.
I've known Sousuke's mom since I was a little kid.
That must have been tough, Yanami-san.
By the way, what is this line for?
It's takoyaki.
I missed out on dessert after lunch, so I thought I'd grab a little something to snack on.
She answered Kaju's question.
First, you need to properly listen to what the other person is saying, Onii-sama.
Please be considerate of Yanami-san's feelings.
As expected, you really get it.
Nukumizu-kun is just like that, isn't he?
Sorry, Yanami-san.
Even without speaking, Onii-sama and I understand each other perfectly.
He has this habit of not saying enough sometimes.
Oh...
I see...
(Yanami is giving me a weird look)
(This is tough...)
Uh...
But more importantly,
Why do we have to stand in line too?
You know,
Food isn't just something you put in your stomach.
Enjoying delicious food and having a conversation with someone.
It fills your heart as well as your stomach.
As expected of Yanami-san.
You have a way with words.
I feel the same way.
Sure, sure, Imouto-chan.
Say more.
Move up a bit so we can fill in the space.
So, does that mean we're eating together too?
But since I've already had lunch, I'm not really hungry.
Yanami-san, didn't you just have lunch too?
Nukumizu-kun
Listen carefully.
Oh, okay.
I'm listening.
You know,
My friend went off to see her boyfriend, so...
I'm all by myself.
I'm about to eat takoyaki.
There is a girl. (? not really sure about this part)
Here's a question for you.
It is.
What should Nukumizu-kun do when he sees such a pitiful girl?
What should he do?
Um, should I just pretend I didn't see it?
Correct!
Just because you're okay being alone, Onii-sama doesn't mean everyone else feels the same way.
Girls can feel like they'll die of loneliness if they're left alone.
So, do you die of loneliness?
So, does that make Yanami some kind of ghost or something?
That's why it's enough just to be by their side without saying anything.
Just sharing takoyaki together is enough.
Imoutou-chan!
You get it!
Nukumizu-kun, listen carefully.
Also, this shop sells takoyaki starting from sets of three.
Even if you're not hungry, you can share it with Kaju and Onii-sama.
Three... pieces... per set...
What's wrong, Yanami-san? You suddenly look so serious.
Wait, it's a set of three?
There are only three pieces in it, you know?
Is there something wrong with that?
Here we go again.
Listen up, Imouto-chan.
In the grand scheme of Earth's history, three is just a rounding error, right?
The history of Earth
Exactly, it's kind of like a concept.
You can't fill your stomach with concepts, can you?
It's no use looking at me like that.
There are things I can do and things I can't.
So basically, the right choice here is the 15-piece set that also looks good for photos.
Look, the 15-piece set comes in a stylish box, doesn't it?
In other words, the stones of the Earth are whispering to me to buy this.
The stones of the Earth...
(Oh no! The light is fading from Kaju's eyes!)
(I can't just leave it like this... I have to do something...)
Um...
You don't really need to worry about how it looks just to eat takoyaki...
Ch-ch-ch...
I have an idea too, you know.
The photos for the literature club's website.
I think it's about time for something new.
Is that... takoyaki?
Yeah, last time I went for a chic vibe with canelés, right?
This time, I'm going for a down-to-earth vibe with takoyaki, playing the role of the "commoner" Yanami-chan.
You know, like how prime ministers often do.
Hasn't Yanami-san always been a commoner?
Are you planning to run for office or something?
I'm considering it for the future...
Of course, absolutely!
Um... Sorry to interrupt the conversation...
Is there a homepage for the literature club?
Ah... We're showcasing the streets of Toyohashi along with photos of the club members.
The photos we uploaded last time got quite a bit of attention.
Lately, the site traffic has been dropping, hasn't it?
I feel like my photos aren't being viewed much...
Isn't it about time we updated it?
That's not true!
Yanami-san's photos are among the top three most accessed overall...
You're really popular!
Top three?!
As expected of Yanami-san!
Really...? Do you think so...?
I guess it does show my good side...
It's one of those things that only those who get it, get it...
Hmm... Huh?
Weren't there only three photos uploaded?
Alright! Let's take some new photos!
Let's take them right now!
Right!
Alright, Yanami-san, it's almost our turn in line.
Excuse me, three orders of 15 pieces, please.
Two of those should be in packs of three!
Hey...
Are you sure you both wanted the packs of three?
It's just a minor detail... It'll be gone in the next moment...
It'll disappear because we're going to eat it...
Alright! Let's find a spot to take a photo...
Then take a picture!
Huh?
In front of the store?
If we don't hurry, it'll get cold.
Ah...
I can smell the takoyaki...
Looks delicious...
(At this rate, Yanami's going to drool in public.)
(I guess there's no choice. Let's just take the picture quickly...)
Alright, alright, I get it.
Okay, I took the picture, so let's eat before it gets cold...
Wait.
Isn't that a bit sloppy?
You know, photographers usually compliment their models to bring out their charm, right?
That's right, Onii-sama.
It's a rare chance to take a picture of Yanami-san, isn't it?
Uh... but it's not really that rare...
Huh?
My photos are super rare, you know!
Didn't you just make me take photos the other day...?
I "made you" take them?!
Onii-sama...
Huh?
Ah... see, people are watching us.
Taking photos of a girl in front of people...
It's embarrassing...
And kind of awkward...
Taking my picture... makes you nervous...
Hmm...
No, it's not because I'm taking a picture of you, Yanami-san.
But because we're in front of people.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
Sure, you should join in too, Imouto-chan.
Me too?
If it's a photo with Imouto-chan, it's like a family picture, right?
It's not embarrassing, is it?
A family photo with just Yanami-san and me...
I see... So that's what you mean!
Hmm? I'm not really sure, but... something like that, I guess?
No, that's not it...
Alright, if we're doing this, let's do it quickly...
Both of you, strike a pose...
Yes, Onii-sama!
Like this?
Ohhh... Imouto-chan... you're so cute...
Alright, Nukumizu-kun, let's take a good photo!
Don't drop the takoyaki!
Okay, I'm taking the picture now!
Let me see!
Looks good!
Oh, it turned out cute!
Huh! Cute?
Maybe...
It probably does...
T older ladies in my neighborhood often say that to me.
Ah...
Kaju looks really good here.
Oh, Onii-sama...
I'm worried about posting it online because it's so cute.
Maybe I should make it accessible only to those within the school.
Even if I do...
Me too...
I'm in the picture, though.
Were you?
Recent software is really impressive.
I'll edit you out.
Why are you editing me out?
See, when there are two people, the screen gets a bit crowded.
It isn't though!
(This person is noisy...)
Well, if it's a family photo, we should definitely include Yanami-san.
I was thinking of making red rice to celebrate the family photo with Yanami-san.
How about joining us?
Is that okay? How many cups of rice are you making? Are you making pork miso soup too?
Well, you see...
Yanami-san is busy, so we shouldn't force her to join us—
I'm free, though...
The friend I had plans with...
She went to see her boyfriend.
Please come over to my place right away.
Is it okay if the pork miso soup is made with red miso?
There's something special about Hatcho miso.
Of course!
When you eat pork miso soup with rice, it's so easy to drink, it's like water.
Then why not just drink water...
Well, I'll do some grocery shopping before heading home.
Please escort Yanami-san to our house, Onii-sama.
That's no good!
Nukumizu-kun can at least help carry the bags.
So can Yanami-san.
I'm just picking up some extra seasonings.
Don't worry about it.
Onii-sama, there's a whole layer cheesecake in the freezer that I made the other day.
Please go home first and serve it to Yanami-san.
Cheesecake?!
Hurry up and get home, Nukumizu-kun!
Well, but you know, we have to eat the takoyaki.
What are you talking about? I already finished eating.
Huh?
Alright, let's go.
Nukumizu-kun, if you don't hurry, the cake will run away!
It's not going anywhere!
Hey, don't pull me!
Well then, you two enjoy yourselves.
(Kaju...l)
(Is she trying to get me alone with Yanami-san?)
(No way)
(But my parents are out too)
(Alone at home with Yanami-san)
This is a bit troublesome.
Did you say something?
I didn't say anything.
(No choice)
(I'll brace myself)
(How much time can I buy with a whole cheesecake?)
(Kaju, please come back soon.)
Hurry up!
Let's go!