I am a first-year student of Tsuwabuki High School
Kazuhiko Nukumizu
I am a member of the Literature Club.
After class, I was invited to
a corner of the "Aquatic Building"
in front of Toyohashi Station by
classmate and fellow club member Anna Yanami.
Yanami-san, why did we
come all the way out here
for the Literature Club homepage?
Didn't you hear?
We were going try and get some cool shots
to make a stylish homepage, remember?
We were?
I didn't say it though.
Wasn't that the vibe I was giving off?
Was it?
It was!
You're in charge of getting the homepage
up and running, so get a grip, Nukumizu-kun.
Ehh, being responsible is tough...
Can I stop?
If that's the case,
why not take the photo here?
Yanami-san, stand over there.
Wait, wait, Nukumizu-kun...
We're taking it here?
We can't?
Did I not say 'stylish'?
This is... this is just a wall!
Uhm...
I was just thinking that that you
look really good with that wall.
I don't though?!!
Really? I think you match that
mortar-covered wall feel.
So, where will we take the photo?
They're selling okonomiyaki over there.
I said 'stylish', didn't I?
Like... something that really fits my image.
Let's find a grammable spot!
Walls and okonomiyaki really fit
your image though...
Oh...
Uh-uhm...
Why not we look for a stylish
ramen or meat restaurant?
How exactly do you see me, Nukumizu-kun?
Ah, an annoying question.
It's gonna be rough if I give a bad answer.
Let me turn it around...
What about you?
Huh?
Of course...
You see me as...
Right, right...
...someone from class
who you've been pining for...
Right.
Wait-
...but is way out of your league.
But when you joined the same club,
and started talking...
...you realized they're really easy to talk to.
Something like that?
I see.
That's how you see me.
Weren't we talking about how
you saw me?
Well, you're not way off the mark
Right? You're not very honest, are you?
Oh! What about over there?
Wait! Don't run!
Coffee and canelé.
This cafe came right up on my
style sensor.
Today's special is "Beef sinew curry."
What should we get, Nukumizu-kun?
We're not getting anything, Yanami-san.
Let's get the photos right away.
Yanami-san, find an inconspicuous corner
so you don't get in the way.
Wait a second.
We need props for the photo, right?
Props?
It's going to be the headliner
on the home page, you know.
So we need a great photo, right?
Your photo is the home page's headliner.
Is that a problem?
Nope, not at all!
Well, grab a pen and--
Alright, let's go in then!
Huh? Wait, why are we going in?
Oh! It's fun to just look at
the canelé here!
Right...
Hey, can't we buy food after
taking the photos?
Nukumizu-kun, we need to buy the
props first, right?
Hmm... Matcha looks good,
but so does roasted green tea.
...though the mature canelés really suit me...
...plain is also hard to pass up...
So these are the props.
There's a lot I want to say, but
anything's fine, right?
But since we're paying with club funds,
we really should think about it.
Club funds?
Why?!
Because we're using them for the home page?
Since we're using it for the
Tsuwabuki Literature Club home page....
...we have to show of Toyohashi's
ambience through its gourmet.
Get a grip, Nukumizu-kun.
Right, I want to go home,
so let's not argue.
Fine, but just one, okay?
Just one.
I know, I know...
Excuse me! Can I have one
of every type of canelé? Takeout.
Did I not just say one?
Which is why I got one of each!
Ah, I'll also have an iced café au lait.
I see, Japanese is hard...
Uhh... I won't order anything.
Okay... let's start with plain.
Stop.
It's a prop for the photo,
so don't eat it yet.
While saying so...
I'm being serious.
Right, stand over there.
I'm taking it with my phone,
so give a good pose.
Like this?
Plain is definitely what we should start with.
I could get addicted to the
texture of this karimocchi.
Ah, even after what I said,
you ate it...
No, wait a second...
I can probably go back home...
Let's go with that.
Huh?
An appetite that can't be resisted...
Exhaustion from a consumerist society...
There's something that resembles
the beauty of a stray dog...
Am I...
...being pitied?
Not at all.
My dad is working, you know...
Look, we got a good photo,
so let's call it a day.
Let's see...
Oh, it looks good.
All that's left is to make it feel stylish...
We're using a stylish restaurant as backing,
so it's plenty stylish.
That's not it.
You know the photos from actors or models?
They just have a really
stylish vibe to them, right?
This doesn't have that...
This isn't good.
I have no idea what Yanami is saying.
This isn't the first time, though.
I don't really get it,
so could you give me an example?
I guess it can't be helped...
Take a look at the photo this
stylish actress took.
It's subtly sepia-ish and cool, right?
It's probably the effect
of the actress' stylish aura.
This is probably just a filter
to make it look more like a film camera.
If we use the filter on a smart phone,
it'll probably look the same.
Filters are meant to make food
look really good, right?
To think they could do more...
They can. As long as you have
a stylish aura.
Get it?
Oh...
Are you okay, Nukumizu-kun?
Isn't having a stylish aura banned?
Just take a good look.
If we change the settings in the app's menu...
Oh!
It's really stylish!
How'd you do that?
Uhh, if you set it to retro mode
and lower the sides...
Right... it becomes stylish.
I see! I totally get it!
She understood that.
Okay, let's take the photo.
Ah, Yanami-san? Where are you going?
We ate all the canelés,
so we need to get replacements.
What? You ate all of them?!
I did.
Why are you so surprised, Nukumizu-kun?
Calm down a little, won't you?
But...
No... this is the sort of woman Yanami is.
Definitely.
Why am I suddenly so shocked?
Yup, that's it. That's what you would do.
That much is obvious.
It's fine if you get it.
Now then, to order one of everything again...
Ah, you'll be paying this time, okay?
Eh?
Because, look...
You're the one who ate all the props.
We can't use any more
club funds than we already have.
I see.
A dictatorship.
People really change when they
are given authority, huh.
If it shuts Yanami up,
then becoming a dictator isn't so bad!
I'll send her to a diet-camp
in the mountains.
Uhm... Club funds belong to everyone, okay?
That means we can't use it just to buy snacks.
Hmm, it can't be helped then.
I'll pull back just this once.
Just this once, okay?
Why does it seem like I'm the one
being unreasonable?
Once again,
a canelé has returned to my hand.
Yes, the last ones were eaten by Yanami-san.
It was delicious, so it can't be helped.
However, this time is different.
Hmm. How so?
My blood sugar level has gone up a little.
I can now endure.
Please praise me!
Yes. I can certainly see
some intelligence in Yanami's eyes right now.
Like a starved husky,
there seems to be a wild madness lying beneath.
Yanami-san, you did really good.
Then, shall we take a photo before
you get hungry.
Can I stand here?
How does it look?
Uhh, a little to the left.
Just enough to see the inside of the store
Aren't I really at the edge?
Am I cut off?
It's fine, it's fine.
The view of this store from the window
is really stylish...
...so if we have to,
we can trim the photo.
The store, okay?
You'll still be in the photo.
I'm counting on you, Nukumizu-kun.
My photogenicity is going to affect
the literature club's future.
This person's self esteem is something else.
Did you say something?
Nope. Nothing!
Okay, I'm taking the photo!
Like this?
Does it look good?
Oh! You look good, you look good!
Your aura is coming out!
You don't sound sincere.
Yes, because I'm not.
Not at all!
Next, take a canelé in your hand,
and act like you're eat--
Just acting, okay?
Don't actually eat it.
I know! The current me is can handle it!
Yanami-san.
Drool.
This isn't good.
The light in Yanami's eyes
is going out.
I have to take it now!
Okay, put the canelé in front of your face.
I'm taking it!
You took it!
Can I eat now?
Yes, I have.
Eat all you want.
Okay, let's dig in!
Yanami looks like she's really
enjoying it.
I wonder if she's eating
properly at home?
Hmm?
Why'd you suddenly take a photo?
Ehh?
No, it's just...
Why did I?...
While watching you eat
the canelé, the shutter just...
Oh?
Nukumizu-kun, are you...
What is it, Yanami-san?
Why are you grinning?
It can be helped.
Here, open wide.
What?
You want to eat too, right?
I'll feed you.
Open wide.
Ah.
No...
Being fed by hand is a little...
What's wrong?
I... washed my hand.
It's not dirty.
When did you wash your hand?
Before I left school.
When I went to the toilet.
Huh...
Anyway, you can eat
without worrying about me.
Yanami is kinda glaring at me.
Scary...
Uhmm...
Want to look at the photo I took?
Look, isn't this really stylish?
Don't you think it looks great?
Your eyes are half closed, but...
The lighting is really good.
Ah, this is--
Isn't this the creep-shot you took earlier?
It's not a creep-shot.
The sight of you naturally eating was...
It was?
Ah. Nothing.
What? I'm gonna get curious, aren't I?
Was this photo really that cute?
Well...
It was.
Eh, Yanami-san? Are you okay?
Here, drink you café au lait.
Nhn. Uhmm...
You suddenly became upfront.
Huh?
Ah, the canelé here are really cute,
so I thought they would make good photos.
Uhm...
What's wrong, Yanami-san?
Yanami-san?
Eh... Why is she angry?
I really don't get this person!
Hey! Wait a second!
That's the problem with you, Nukumizu-kun!