I'm curious about her... Maybe I'll go have a chat with her.
...Oh no...
What should I do...?
Are you in trouble?
Huh? Oh!
Um... well... let's see...
I'm sorry for startling you. I'm Utsumi, a student from the Producer Department.
I'm Lilja Katsuragi.
I'm sorry for getting startled...
No, it's my fault for approaching you so suddenly. I just couldn't help but notice you seemed a bit lost.
Um...
I can't seem to find where the chapel is...
Would you like me to walk with you part of the way? I'm headed in that direction too.
Huh...?
Um... that would be really helpful.
Could I ask you for a favor?
Oh, so you just arrived in Japan, Katsuragi?
Yes.
I came over here when I enrolled.
I'm surprised. Your Japanese is really natural for someone who just arrived.
My father is Japanese.
And I've been learning from my Japanese friend, too...
Will I really be able to communicate properly at a Japanese school?
I was really worried about it...
Hearing that from you, Senpai, makes me feel a bit more at ease.
Senpai?
You call someone older who attends the same school "Senpai," right?
Um...
Maybe...
Did I make a mistake with my Japanese?
No, there's no problem.
May I ask you something? Why did you choose to come to this academy, Katsuragi?
My friend invited me.
She said we should become idols together.
She said, "Let's go to an idol school so we can become idols."
I'm... not very confident.
At first, I thought about turning it down...
Was there something that changed your mind?
I watched a live performance.
At this academy. Together with my friend.
It was amazing.
It was really...
It was truly incredible.
So then...
Um... well...
"I want to be like that too."
That's how I've come to feel.
Of course, it's presumptuous of me.
I'm clumsy, and I'm not cute either.
But still,
Even so,
No matter what,
I want to become an idol.
...You have a good look in your eyes. I'm sure you can make it.
Do you really think so?
Lilja, what do you think is the most important talent for an idol to have?
Huh?
Um...
Being cute, or being good at singing and dancing, maybe?
That's very important, but it's not the most important thing.
It's... difficult...
Being able to speak well, maybe?
The most important talent for an idol isn't that. The most crucial talent is...
Having a strong will.
The talent to have courage and take a step towards your dreams.
No way...
I... I don't have any courage.
You do have it.
You decided to become an idol and convinced your parents, didn't you?
Yes, that's true.
You studied hard, took the exams, passed, and left your family to come to Japan.
This is a foreign land. It's natural to feel anxious. You might not even be sure if you'll be understood properly.
But here you are now.
...I really want to become one, no matter what.
That day, I dreamed of becoming an idol.
...And here you are.
I originally just intended to have a chat, but... I've changed my mind.
Senpai?
Katsuragi.
Please allow me to be your producer.
What? ...No way!?
M-me...? Are you serious...?
Absolutely. Let's aim even higher than just admiration. Let's strive to become a top idol.
It's an honor.
But I'll do it.
I want to give it a try.
Um, please—
I'm counting on you, Senpai!
I ended up scouting her on impulse... but I'm sure she'll become a wonderful idol.
Um...
I'm looking forward to working with you starting today.
Yes, let's work hard together.
I'll do my best.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'm glad to see your enthusiasm. Let's start by talking about your lessons.
Um, okay.
So, what should I do first?
What do you think I should do instead?
Uh, um...
Everything...?
Well, to put it simply, yes.
But there's no need to worry. You're a complete beginner, right, Katsuragi?
...Yes.
I've never had any experience with singing or dancing.
I don't even know how to approach the lessons...
Even if I throw myself into the lessons,
I don't really feel like it's making much of a difference...
The producer's job is to help with those kinds of things.
I've come up with a lesson plan.
So, where should we start?
You're talking about the lessons, right...?
What should I do...?
Alright, let's focus on strengthening your singing first.
Singing, huh...?
So, vocal lessons?
Yes. Trying to do everything at once from the start will just lead to confusion.
Okay.
That's how I've been up until now, isn't it?
Everything just ends up being half-baked...
Let's take it one step at a time and move forward steadily. Today, we'll start with vocal exercises.
Got it.
You're really dependable, Senpai.
Well, I am a producer, after all.
...I'm really happy.
Having someone I can rely on is...
Relieving.
...I just arrived in Japan, and...
I don't have many friends, so I feel a bit lonely.
I do have one close friend, though.
I've been relying too much on her...
From now on, I'll be here with you. If anything comes up, feel free to rely on me.
...Okay.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for choosing someone like me.
I want to live up to your expectations, Senpai.
And so, I'll become an idol.
Lilja, could you say that again?
I'll become an idol.
Louder, please.
W-what?
It's embarrassing.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about. No one at this school will laugh at that dream.
Yeah, you're right...
So, declare it with confidence. Speak loudly and clearly.
Y-yes...!
I will become an idol...!
Your voice is still a bit quiet. Try to imagine projecting it from your diaphragm.
It's already night, isn't it? Let's call it a day.
Huff, huff...
My stomach... it kind of hurts...
Ah, it's muscle soreness. You use your muscles for diaphragmatic breathing, after all.
But... but... I can still keep going.
...Really? You already look exhausted, though.
For someone like me to become an idol, I'm sure...
I can't just be like everyone else.
I need to put in more time and effort than anyone else.
...Alright. If you can say that, Katsuragi.
But let's take a short break. There's no point in pushing yourself to the point of exhaustion.
Haa, haa...
Got it.
It's great that you're so motivated. Really.
Thanks to you, Senpai, I was able to have a really great lesson.
...I'm still lacking in skills, though.
I feel like I've grown just a little bit.
It's been a long time since I've felt this way...
That's why I'm happy.
If you feel like you've grown, that's the result of your hard work, Katsuragi.
All I can do as the Producer is lend a helping hand.
Senpai...
I hope you don't feel too accomplished just yet.
Lilja, you still have so much room to grow. Today is just the first step.
Is that really the case...?
I'll pave the way for you to become an idol. All you need to do, Katsuragi, is keep moving forward.
But...
Can someone like me really...
Can I really become one?
You can do it, absolutely.
I will make you an idol. Please believe in my words.
Senpai...
I'm sorry.
I keep saying negative things—
I, I will...!
I will become an idol!!
...! You've got great volume. It looks like today's vocal practice really paid off.
Hehe... I'm so happy.
Thank you so much, Senpai.
Let's make a note of today's production status.
Her enthusiasm and determination is impressive. Let's keep this up and gradually build her skills.
How did I do?
Your vocal exercises have really helped stabilize your volume.
Hehe... I'm so happy.
Well...
Um... Is there something that's bothering you?
Hmm, well, it's a bit tricky to say right now, but—
I've noticed your expression is a bit stiff, and it's been on my mind.
Expression, you mean?
Alright. Katsuragi, what kind of expression did the idol you like have on stage?
She was smiling and looked like she was having so much fun.
She looked like she was having such a great time.
I felt happy too.
I felt energized.
Now it's your turn, Katsuragi, to bring energy to everyone.
Okay, got it...!
It's great that you're serious about your lessons, but how about practicing your expressions for the real performance as well?
Specifically, try to smile more. Even while you're singing, make a conscious effort to keep smiling.
A smile, huh?
I feel kind of embarrassed.
Have confidence. Your smile is really cute, Katsuragi.
C-cute?
M-me...?
Hehe...
Yes, that's the expression.
H-huh?
This isn't really a smile, is it?
That's perfect. A genuine smile is always best.
Well...
Because it made me happy...
I know it might be difficult, but your expression is part of the performance too.
Katsuragi, I'me sure a gentle expression suits you better.
I'm not confident, though.
But I want to get closer to that sparkling smile.
That's the spirit.
Alright, here goes.
—Senpai.
What is it?
L-like this?
What exactly is that...?
Um, well...
I was trying to smile...
Could you try to make it look a bit more natural?
I'm sorry...
Did I really look that bad...?
It's not that, but you were trying too hard and ended up making a funny face.
Let's try to smile more naturally. Just relax, relax.
Y-yes. Um...
L-like this...?
Oh, I can't believe you're laughing, Senpai...
Huh? Did I mess something up...?
I'm sorry. It's just that your expression was a bit amusing... hahaha.
In a way, it seems like you have a talent for uplifting everyone.
No, I think you're heading in the wrong direction...
No, but... that face you made earlier... haha.
Please, don't laugh so much.
I'll start laughing too.
That's a much better smile than before.
Well, it's because you were laughing so much, Senpai...
But somehow, I think I get it now.
A natural, genuine smile is good enough, isn't it?
I'll give it a try.
In front of the mirror.
...Right... making the face you did just now in front of a mirror might actually be good practice.
What do you mean by that?
No, no! It's nothing. Ahem, ahem!
...Um, Senpai?
Anyway, let's work hard on our practice.
On stage, in front of a large audience, to be able to inspire and energize everyone.
Got it…!
Let's make a note of today's production status.
Her smile will be a great asset. Let's keep refining it.
(...She's improving.)
(Even if she's taking it one step at a time)
I've finished the lesson menu...
Great job. Take a break.
Your expression has softened a bit.
Really? Are you sure?
I'm glad I've been practicing.
...Oh, I'm a bit thirsty, so...
I'll go buy a drink.
Got it.
Lilja's taking a while...
I'll go check on her.
...Senpai is a really good person.
He's kind, knowledgeable, and capable of anything.
He's really guiding me.
(Oh, she's talking with her friends.)
Wow, that's nice. I wish I had a Producer too.
I know, right? I'm really jealous.
But it's strange, isn't it? Why Lilja, of all people?
Huh...?
Oh, sorry. I didn't mean it in a bad way.
You know, there are plenty of other good students around, right?
Yeah, I guess you're right...
I'm not doing well in my classes either...
I didn't mean it like that. I'm just wondering why it had to be Lilja.
Yeah, it is a bit strange, isn't it? I mean, I don't want to sound rude, but...
It's not like you're particularly good at singing or dancing, and you don't really stand out appearance-wise either...
...Yeah, that's right.
Because I saw something special in her.
When it comes to producing idols, no other reason is necessary.
Oh, Senpai...?
Sorry, I didn't mean to eavesdrop, but—
I overheard some not-so-great comments about the idol I'm working with.
Oh, no, that's not what I meant... right?
Uh, yeah...
I believe Katsuragi can become a top idol.
That's why I'm producing you. ...Let's go, Katsuragi.
Oh, Senpai...!
I'm sorry, both of you.
I'm going...!
I'm sorry. I got a bit carried away.
...No, I was happy.
You were protecting me, weren't you?
It's just how I really feel. ...Are you okay, Katsuragi?
...I already knew.
I already knew without anyone else having to tell me.
I don't have any talent.
...Katsuragi.
But that's just a given.
That's not a reason to give up.
Um, Senpai...
I'm really happy.
Even so, I want to believe in myself.
So let's practice.
I can still keep pushing myself.
...It's because you can say things like that, Katsuragi, that I decided to produce you.
You may not have any standout talents. But that's your one, your only—
—and greatest weapon.
...It might not be my only one.
Up until now, just having that was enough.
Now I have you by my side, Senpai.
...Thanks to that, I can work harder than ever before.
Lilja...
I'm going to become an idol!
Being a top idol... that's a bit much for me...
Honestly, I'm not that confident...
Try to play it cool.
Well then, just aim to be a regular idol.
...Uh... I'm sorry.
I think I'll try to be a top idol.
Well said. Let's continue with the lessons.
To become a top idol, we'll push hard. Really hard!
Eek...
The Producer seems a bit intimidating...
But, but I'll do it!
Please be tough on me!
Let's reorganize the report.
Her passion and determination to become an idol are genuine. I'm sure she'll keep getting better and better.
Hello, Senpai.
Thank you for your support today.
Hello, Katsuragi.
Starting today, we'll gradually move into more practical lessons.
Yes...!
Up until now, we've focused almost exclusively on vocal lessons.
We've only done the bare minimum to address weaknesses, like practicing facial expressions.
Yes, that's right...
Basically, it's been about vocal exercises, breathing techniques, pronunciation, pitch control, and rhythm strengthening—
After that, it's just singing over and over, correcting as I go...
I've been doing a lot of practical training.
Yes. It's steady progress, but you're growing little by little.
...Am I getting any better?
I don't really feel it yet.
It's okay. If you're feeling unsure, would you like to watch some of the early recordings?
Recordings, you say...?
Yes. We always keep a record of our daily lessons.
...Ah, here it is. This is the recording from your first day of lessons.
―This is...
Not great, is it?
I can barely hear my voice at all...
And I couldn't maintain pitch either.
The rhythm too...
Alright, let me show you the next recording. This is from yesterday.
Huh...?
Huh, what's this...?
Um, well...
I think I might be getting a little better, at least for me.
Yes. You're growing, Lilja.
It seems like it, doesn't it...?
Seeing this, I understand that.
...But I still have a long way to go.
Of course, that's exactly right. There's still plenty of room for growth.
It's not a skill that improves overnight. Let's build it up steadily, step by step.
Y-yes...!
Starting today, let's focus more on the fundamentals.
You're going to gain what you need to stand on that stage, Katsuragi.
What am I missing...?
Imagine yourself standing on that stage right now.
Me, on stage...
A large audience is watching. They're eagerly anticipating your performance, Katsuragi.
Just like you did, with eyes sparkling...
They're all here... just to see me.
...Your hands are shaking. You're not comfortable in front of people, are you, Katsuragi?
...Yes, that's right.
I'm not really good at it.
...I'm aiming to become an idol, so I can't let this hold me back, right...?
But it's not that I dislike it.
I just get so nervous...
Being nervous isn't a bad thing. It just shows how serious you are about this.
What you're missing, Katsuragi, is experience — specifically, experience performing in front of an audience.
I'm starting to get nervous...
You mean practicing performing in front of people, right?
Exactly. Little by little, you'll get used to being in front of people.
Do you think it might be a bother to have them practice with someone like me...?
Don't worry. I'll call over some students from the Idol Course.
Watching and learning is also part of the lesson. I'm sure they'll be willing to help.
Oh... I understand...
Huh, there's no one here. Even though class has already started.
Seriously. I wonder what that's all about.
Today's lesson is all about learning by watching.
Eek...
There are more people than I expected...
I can't do it, Senpai... It's impossible.
Compared to the actual performance, this is a much smaller crowd, you know?
Y-yeah... I guess you're right...
Just relax. Just sing like you always do.
Y-yes.
Just like always, just like always...
Remember, this is just a lesson.
Think of this as the real thing.
Th-this is the real thing...
Uh, oh no no no...
(I don't expect her to get it right from the start.)
(What's important is developing an awareness for the real performance.)
I'm Lilja Katsuragi.
I'll sing...!
Oh, thank you so much...
Don't get too down about it. It's normal for a first try.
Try to relax a bit more. You've got this!
It feels kind of nostalgic, doesn't it? We learned a lot too!
Y-yeah...
Great job today. You really worked hard.
...But it was a complete disaster.
Even after all that practice, my voice was shaking, and I couldn't sing well at all...
If I perform like this in the real thing... I'll just end up disappointing everyone.
If things stay as they are now, yes. But only if things stay as they are.
It's just like before. It's okay to take it step by step and gradually improve.
You can do it. I believe in you, Katsuragi.
Senpai...
Thank you so much.
Thank you for believing in me.
Thanks to you, Senpai, I've realized so many of my weaknesses.
I believe that you can overcome this, Katsuragi.
I'll face myself, too.
So this time, I'll make sure to—
I'll be able to sing in front of everyone...!
I'll make a note of today's production status.
Overcoming stage fright is absolutely essential. Now, how should we proceed...
Thank you so much...
(She's gradually improving. Now it's just a matter of being concious of it.)
I'm sorry...
I couldn't do it well again today...
Lilja, let's talk about something fundamental for a moment.
Something fundemental...?
What could it be...?
I believe that being an idol is a profession where you let people see who you truly are.
By showing your shining self, you captivate people and inspire them to dream.
...Yes, that's true.
...So that's what being an idol is all about...
But right now, Katsuragi, you're afraid to show your true self.
...Yes.
Why do you think that is?
...Because I lack confidence.
In myself, and in my performance.
...I just can't believe that someone like me could move people's hearts.
That's why you get so tense and close yourself off, hoping no one will notice you.
...Yes.
It's okay to not be perfect.
...Huh?
Of course, it's always better to do things well.
Yeah, you're right...
But technique isn't everything. What really matters is the heart.
During the last lesson, were you thinking about the audience?
...I was just trying to do it well earlier.
I was just focused on trying to do it well...
The people who were watching me...
…I wasn't thinking about them.
It's true that technique is important. But technique alone won't reach people's hearts.
What matters most is the intention to connect with others. Show them the best of yourself.
I'm sorry...
I'm so nervous that I can't do anything...
Giving it my all and doing my best.
That was the only thing I had going for me.
I was truly drawn to your strong will, unbreakable spirit, and earnest dedication, Katsuragi.
Even if your skills are still developing, Katsuragi, your performance will surely touch people's hearts.
Senpai...
...Thank you so much.
I feel like I've woken up.
The person I am now,
I'll show the audience everything I've got right now.
With everything I have, I'll move people's hearts...!
That's the spirit. I'm sure you can do it, Katsuragi.
Let's continue with the same lessons starting tomorrow.
...Senpai.
I have a suggestion.
What is it? It's rare to get a suggestion from you, Katsuragi.
For the next lesson,
Can I invite a friend?
Of course, that's fine, but why?
...She's my best friend.
To me, she's one of a kind.
I want Sumika to see who I am now.
I want to reach her heart.
She's someone I truly feel that way about.
So, you want to show her first, is that it?
...Yes.
I thought this might help overcome my fear of being in front of people.
Understood.
As your Producer, I want to respect your wishes as much as possible.
Thank you so much...!
It will definitely reach her.
The person I am now will reach her heart.
I'll make a note of today's production progress.
I'm sure that with the person Lilja is now, she'll be able to reach her best friend's heart.
Is this the right place?
This is such a weird lesson, isn't it?
Just watching someone else's lesson...
Welcome, Sumika Shiun. I've been expecting you.
Hi there! Are you the person from the Producer Course who invited me?
Yes, I'm the Producer. Please, come this way.
Oh, Sumika!
What, Lilja!?
Is today's lesson going to be...
...Yeah.
I'm going to sing.
Wow, I'm really looking forward to it!
You've been working really hard lately!
Yeah.
Because I want to become an idol.
I see.
I'm still not as good as you, Sumika, but...
I want you to see who I am now...
I asked Senpai for help.
What are you talking about, Lilja?
You shouldn't compare yourself to someone like me.
...Sumika, are you really not interested in becoming an idol anymore?
Hmm, it's not that I'm not interested, but it might be a bit difficult for me.
Oh, but my love for idols hasn't changed at all!
I'm cheering for you too, Lilja!
I'll be here to support you as a friend!
I'm really looking forward to today's lesson if Lilja is going to sing!
...Okay.
Watch me, Sumika.
Alright, Katsuragi, please get ready.
Yes!
Have you given up on becoming an idol?
...Did you hear what we were talking about earlier?
I didn't say that at all.
But you know, becoming an idol isn't something that happens easily, right?
I'm not really serious about it.
And I can't get as into it as Lilja has.
That's kind of what I'm thinking, but am I wrong?
...No, I don't think so. Everyone has their own way of living.
My friend invited me.
We decided to become idols together.
...She's my best friend.
To me, she's one of a kind.
I want Sumika to see who I am now.
I want to reach her heart.
She's someone I truly feel that way about.
Listening to her sing is nice and all, but what exactly is this lesson supposed to be about?
...Lilja struggles with being in front of people, so she's training to overcome that.
Oh, right, that makes sense.
Lilja gets pretty nervous, you know.
Lilja said she wanted you to see her.
She wants to show you the person she's become.
Oh, is that so?
She doesn't have to go through all the trouble...
I already know she's amazing.
Yes, that's right. Katsuragi is truly amazing. I can really feel it as her producer.
Please stay and watch Katsuragi's performance.
Hmm, if you're going to say that much, I guess I'll have to look forward to it!
I'm ready!
Can I start right away?
Alright. Let's get started.
Yes!
Watch me, Sumika.
Lilja Katsuragi... I'm going to sing!
Hah, hah...
So, how was it, Sumika...?
Wow! That was amazing!
That's the Lilja I believed in!
Lilja, your performance just now was fantastic.
Really? I'm so glad...
I actually sang it properly.
I've gained a little bit of confidence.
It's all thanks to you and Sumika.
That's good to hear. However, there were a few mistakes.
Uh... y-yes...
I know that myself...
I'll practice where I made mistakes, and next time, I'll sing even better...!
That's the spirit.
You're really giving it your all!
It's like you're a completely different person from just a little while ago.
I'm still inexperienced, but...
It's all thanks to  Senpai for guiding me.
…I may not have talent, but
He gave me the push I needed.
I can move forward little by little.
Oh, I see.
I'm really glad to hear that.
You found a good producer, didn't you?
Lilja's really shining right now, even just a little bit.
...Sumika.
Thank you for coming today.
Thanks to Sumika.
I feel like I've changed a little.
I realized that what's important is the desire to reach out and connect.
Until yesterday, Katsuragi seemed to shrink under the audience's gaze.
If this lesson helped you find a way to overcome your challenges, that's the most important thing.
Yes, Senpai.
I think I'm okay now.
I'm not really sure, but...
I'm glad I could be of help to Lilja.
If anything comes up, just let me know, okay?
I'm free, so I'm always here to help!
Hehe, when Lilja becomes an idol, I'm going to brag about being one of her original fans!
...Sumika, I haven't given up on our promise.
...What promise was that again?
I forget things so easily, you know?
...Well, I guess it's time for me to head out!
I've got a friend calling me, so...
Good luck, Lilja!
See you later, Producer!
...Katsuragi.
...Shall we get back to the lesson?
...Are you sure about this?
...Yes.
I'm okay.
I believe in Sumika.
Sumika's talent and mine... they're just not comparable.
Until Sumika gets back, I need to catch up, even just a little.
...Yes, that's right. Let's make sure you can keep your promise.
Yes!
Let's make a note of today's production status.
For now, she's taken a step forward. I'm sure her relationship with her best friend will too...
Lilja, I've got some good news for you.
Senpai?
What is it?
The date for the live performance has been set. It's going to be your first live show, Katsuragi.
Huh?
You look completely taken aback.
W-wait, a live show...!?
Isn't it too soon for me...?
It's true that up until now, we've focused on the basics...
Based on your progress, Katsuragi, I've decided it's time for you to move on to the next step.
A l-live, me...?
You don't need to worry so much; you'll be fine.
Idol course students grow by experiencing live performances repeatedly.
A l-live performance... me...?
Are you okay?
Y-yes...!
I-I-I-I'll do my best...!
I-I'm sorry...
I'm just so nervous, it's getting to me...
Please calm down. It's still a ways off.
But, still...
You've gotten to the point where you can sing confidently in front of others. You'll be just fine, Katsuragi.
Believe in yourself. You can do it, Katsuragi.
...Yes.
Alright, shall we start the lesson? From today, we'll gradually incorporate some dance as well.
A live performance...
—Four hours after the lesson ended.
I can't believe I left my house keys at school... How careless of me...
Hmm? The lights are still on... Is someone still in the practice room?
...Hah, Hah...!
This isn't good enough... This just won't do...
Better, better, I need to get even better...!
Hah, Hah... Cough, cough!
I need to energize everyone.
I need to give a great performance...
I'll deliver my song to everyone's hearts...
...Katsuragi.
...Oh, Senpai?
Wh-why are you here so late...?
That's what I should be saying to you. Have you really been practicing all this time since then?
I just couldn't sit still.
I won't make it as I am now...
I need to try harder...
Huh, what...?
—Katsuragi!
...I'm sorry.
I'm feeling a bit unsteady on my feet...
...Katsuragi. Let's call it a day and head home.
It's true that hard work is important. But overworking yourself will only harm your health.
But as I am now...
I'm still not good enough at singing or dancing...
Are you really that scared? Of your first live performance?
...My body just starts trembling on its own.
I'm just not there yet...
I think it's too soon for a live performance...
Alright, I understand.
Let's just call it a day and head home. How about taking a break tomorrow?
I'm sorry, Senpai.
—The next day.
Senpai, what brings you here today?
I told you, we're taking a break.
I can't believe you're actually taking a break, Senpai...
Usually, it's all about lessons, lessons, and more lessons...
Is that really the impression you have?
Maybe I should have been a bit kinder to Katsuragi.
Oh, it's almost time. Let's hurry, shall we?
...Where are we going?
You'll find out soon enough. I've already got the tickets.
- The concert venue
Wow...!
For people like us, I thought this would be the best way to unwind.
...I'm so happy.
It's been a while since I've been to a live show.
The ones who were just on stage are all students from the Idol Course.
They were so confident up there, and yet they're students just like me...
This is part of your learning too. Let's observe and learn from how they carry themselves.
...Huh?
Isn't today supposed to be a break?
...You're right.
...Of course, I'm just kidding.
I didn't know you could joke around, Senpai.
It's unusual and refreshing.
You wouldn't want to forget that enjoying the performance is what's most important, right?
I thought it would be a good idea for you to reaffirm the place you're aiming for, Katsuragi.
Senpai...
How did you feel watching those idols?
They're really amazing...
Everyone's so dazzling and cool.
Next time, it'll be you, Katsuragi, standing on that stage.
Doesn't it make you excited?
I'm sure it'll be a lot of fun.
...Yes, it really is.
I want to stand there as soon as possible, too.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
Yes, truly...
I remembered the reason why I first wanted to become an idol.
Watching the school live performance with Sumika...
...I just admired it.
I want to stand on that stage too.
I want to sing and dance to lift everyone's spirits.
You can do it, Katsuragi, with the way you are now.
I understand you're nervous. But there's no need to be scared or intimidated.
Senpai...
Let's enjoy it. After all, it's your first live performance.
Enjoy it... Yes, you're right.
This is the place I've been aiming for.
Alright... Once the live performance is over, I need to get back to practicing...!
That's not a good idea. Take it easy and rest today.
Oh, no...
No need to look so defeated. We'll get back to our rigorous schedule starting tomorrow.
Really?
I'm so happy, thank you so much...!
I'll do my best to make our first live show a success...!
Let's go over the report again.
With the Lilja Katsuragi we have now, I'm sure she'll be just fine. I hope she enjoys the live show.
—The day of the first live show.
The day has finally arrived.
Wow... I can't believe there are so many people here.
Are you nervous?
Yeah, I guess so...
My heart is pounding.
It's the time and emotion you've invested up to this point.
It's definitely not a bad thing.
I've always aimed for this place.
It's the stage I've dreamed of.
Right now, I just want to enjoy it.
I won't say it's okay to be bad or offer any consolation.
…I understand what you're trying to say, Senpai.
I'll just do my very best and show everyone what I can do right now.
Lilja.
Huh?
You can do it.
Just like always.
...I understand!
...Senpai.
I'm going to become an idol!
...! Katsuragi...
Please watch over me.
—Katsuragi!
Oh, Senpai...
How did I do...?
I gave it everything I had, but...
Oh, but...
I messed that up, and I messed this up too...
Ugh...
That was an amazing performance.
Really?
Yes. Because everyone in the audience was smiling and having a great time, weren't they?
Your hard work, Katsuragi, truly touched everyone's hearts.
You might have noticed, but she was in the audience too.
...Yes.
I saw her from the stage.
Do you think it reached Sumika's heart too?
I'm sure it reached her. Your singing, Katsuragi, has that power.
Senpai...
...That being said, it's true there were quite a few mistakes.
Yeah, you're right...
I'm sorry...
I guess I'm not cut out to be a producer.
W-What!?
I decided to produce you because I saw your strong determination.
However, in reality, I felt that the obstacles standing in your way, Katsuragi, were quite high and challenging.
But I was wrong.
Katsuragi, you're an even more amazing idol than I ever imagined.
It's all thanks to you, Senpai.
I couldn't have done anything on my own.
You've brought me this far, Senpai.
So, um... really, thank you.
Thank you so much, Senpai.
We're just getting started.
Let's keep working hard together from here on out.
Yes...!
Let's keep working hard together, always!
I look forward to working with you from now on, Senpai!
Let's make a note of today's production status.
That was a fantastic performance with everyone smiling! She's an amazing idol!
Oh? Katsuragi? Isn't today supposed to be a day off?
Oh, hi there, Senpai.
I'm sorry, I just couldn't help myself...
I just didn't want to lose the feeling from yesterday's live performance.
I just wanted to practice a bit more.
I told you before, overworking isn't good for you, remember?
Uh, well, it's just for a little bit...
I promise I won't overdo it like last time!
I'll let it slide just for today.
Well, I guess there's no helping it.
Really? Are you sure?
I'm so happy...!
I'm always amazed by your enthusiasm, Katsuragi.
...The live performance was so much fun.
I just can't calm down from all the excitement.
I want to stand on that stage again.
Next time, I want to sing even better.
I want to dance well.
Even when I tried to rest, it was all I could think about, and I just couldn't sit still.
Before I knew it, I was practicing.
If you're practicing with that much enthusiasm, there's no way I could stop you.
Hello! Sorry to intrude.
Is Lilja here?
Oh, Sumika!?
Ah, I finally found you!
I've been looking for you!
Yesterday, you were asleep when I got back, and by the time I woke up, you were already gone.
I'm sorry.
As soon as I got back, I just felt so drained...
No worries—your performance was amazing!
...Thank you.
I could see you from the stage.
Really? Are you serious?
There were so many people in the audience, I'm surprised you managed to spot me.
I was looking for you.
I was hoping to find you, Sumika.
Wow! You like me too much, don't you?
You're making me blush saying things like that.
If I'm imagining things, it's embarrassing, but towards the end, were you crying a little?
...I wasn't crying!
I mean, I was really moved, though...
No, you were definitely crying.
Don't say unnecessary things!
I just got something in my eye, that's all!
Haha...
Thank you, Sumika.
Thank you for coming to my live performance.
...I just wanted to see it myself.
It's nothing to be thanked for.
Actually, I'm the one who should be thanking you.
After seeing a performance like that, well...
I just can't give up.
Sumika...
Seeing you spread your wings like that, I thought, "I want to be like that too."
I want to stand next to Lilja and soar even higher.
I feel the same way... I want that too.
Sumika...!
I'm sorry about when I went to watch your lesson.
I pretended not to remember our promise.
I actually do remember it clearly.
I actually remembered it clearly.
But I just didn't have the courage to try again, so I couldn't say it...
...Yeah, I know.
I believed in you, Sumika.
Listening to you singing gave me the courage to keep trying.
Watching your live performance, you know,
You're working so hard and giving it your all...
I feel like I need to try even harder too.
You made me feel that way.
I'm sure everyone who watched felt the same.
...I'm glad it reached you.
I'm still inexperienced, but...
My singing can change someone.
It reaches the hearts of those I want to touch.
Yeah, Lilja, you're amazing.
I knew it from the start!
Thank you, Sumika.
Thank you for inviting me to become an idol.
If you hadn't been there for me,
I probably wouldn't have been able to find the courage.
You were the one who took my hand and led me.
And Senpai gave me that push forward.
Because of that, I'm here now.
So when you seemed like you were going to quit,
I thought, "Now it's my turn."
This time, it's my turn to reach out to you.
Lilja...
Hey, Sumika.
Let's become idols together, the two of us.
...Yeah.
Absolutely, we will.
I'll catch up to you soon, Lilja.
Promise.
Yeah, it's a promise.
Sorry for interrupting your lesson.
That's all I wanted to say.
No, it's okay.
Oh, right.
Here's a little treat for you.
Feel free to have it during your break.
Producer, too. Please have some too if you'd like!
Thank you.
Thanks, Sumika.
No worries at all!
Good luck with your practice!
You too, Sumika! Do your best!
Of course!
I'm off to my lesson now, too!
See you later!
You've got a really good friend.
Yes, really...
I'm sure she'll catch up. In the meantime, let's keep moving forward.
Yeah, that's right...
I'll keep working hard, step by step.
That's the spirit, Katsuragi.
It's because you're here to support someone like me that I can keep moving forward.
Thank you so much.
...for choosing me.
I didn't even know where to start.
You guided me when I was lost in the darkness—
You showed me the way.
I saw the light in the direction where you were, Senpai.
...You're exaggerating. To me, you're the one who's the light, Katsuragi.
All I can do is help you shine even brighter, Katsuragi.
...Even so, I'm grateful.
Actually, I'm the one who should be thanking you.
You gave us such an amazing performance.
...Senpai.
This isn't the end, you know? Katsuragi, we're just getting started.
After all, the goal is to become a top idol.
Yes!
If you're there to support me, then—
I will become a top idol!