(Yukko) April 1st
On that day, while facing the sunset,
I shouted loudly.
Our fight ends here!
GOODBYE MY JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL！
(Mio) April 2nd
Tomorrow is the school entrance ceremony.
I'm so nervous.
I can't dress embarrassingly, right?
What should I wear?
Obviously the school uniform, right!
(Mai) April 3rd.
First years.
Shiny.
Everyone, Congratulations for enrollment.
Thank you.
(Yukko) April 4th.
Cherry blossoms bloom...
I'll show you how to make them bloom...
lesser cuckoo.
Yukko.
(Hakase) April 5th.
Hakase is wearing a lab coat.
Because I'm a professor!
Yay! It's warm!
(Nano) April 6th.
The other day, Hakase was able to put on Pajamas by herself for the first time.
While humming to herself, she changed into her pajamas.
...and made a peace sign with a satisfied look on her face.
I think it is really great.
So, for a while, I won't tell her that...
...she buttoned her shirt wrong.
(Yukko) April 7th.
NEW DAY！
My new school life is beginning.
MY HEART EXCITING AND WONDER！
Flying towards the future like an arrow.
In English...
?????
The runner on third tagged up and slid home, or something like that.
(Mai) April 8th
Today's Buddha statue.
Ushusama Myō-ō
Also known as "The Toilet God."
Tomorrow, I think I'll leave it in the toilet.
(Yukko) April 9th.
Tomorrow is the day I've been waiting for—Sunday!
Yo! I've been waiting!
Oh, how exciting!
(Hakase) April 10th.
Since today is "Opposite Day,"
I'm wearing my lab coat backwards.
But Nano said, "You're wearing it backwards," and made me change.
That's not it!
Today is "Opposite Day," so backwards is fine!
(Yukko) April 11th.
Ah, MONDAY.
Why are you MONDAY?
(Hakase) April 12th.
Baumkuchen is delicious!
Because it's... round!
(Nano) April 13th.
Ah!
The baumkuchen I bought yesterday is gone!
Even though I was planning to eat it with Hakase...!
Geez, Hakase...
If you're going to eat it, at least say something!
(Sasahara) April 14th.
Today's lunch.
Was it... Maezawa Beef?
It's just as I like it—well.
Not only can you enjoy the taste of the meat...
You can enjoy the chewiness.
It was quite delicious.
????
You've really done it.
(Sakurai-sensei) April 15th.
Last week, I think I might have been seeing things.
I think... there was...
A goat at school.
Is someone keeping it at the bicycle parking area?
So, that means...
Someone bought a goat?
But letting it run free is a problem
I'll ask Tomiyoka-sensei...
What I should do.
(Tachibana Misato) April 16th.
Geez.
What's he thinking using a goat to come to school?
Even if its a school road,
Cars use this road too.
I get nervous because of how dangerous it is.
Of course, I'm worried about the cars.
(Yukko) April 17th.
I've got it! Let's make a song called "Flying Akabeko!"
Songs about personal experiences are super popular now!
Is this an unexpected comeback?
"Produced by Yukko?"
Even the name has a nice ring to it!
It's like a bonus for the series.
(Mai) April 18th.
Yukko observation memo.
Puns.
Sometimes poems.
In some places "Selamat Pagi."
The back of her head.
No abnormalities.
She was off her guard, so...
She equipped squid tentacles.
Sense of humour.
+3.
(Mio) April 19th.
You're definitely out!
April 20th.
The 3-second rule is...
The rule of the soul!
Those who laugh in 3 seconds, die in 3 seconds!
(Mai) April 21st.
The way Miroku Bosatsu sits...
With one leg crossed over the other.
Showing numbness.
There's no such thing...
...as a momentary dilemma.
(Hakase) April 22nd.
Hakase used all the milk in her experiments.
We are out of milk...
...because of the experiments.
It's not something I did.
(Mio's Sister)
Should I attack with flavour?
With smell?
I've been worrying about this problem all week.
But all those troubles disappear when I see my sister's face.
The world is strange.
(Mio) April 24th.
Thanks to my sister, my Sunday was wasted.
(Principal) April 25th.
Monday.
This morning's assembly...
Everyone was so cold, huh...
Even though its still shuatsu(?)...
The first-years are already becoming like the current students...
The principal was lonely...
I really don't want to go to school tomorrow.
(Yukko) April 26th.
Why does this Math exist in this world?
WHY？
I can't focus on my homework with an unanswerable question like that!
So, I'll take a break!
I meant to take a break, but I ended up watching the entire 30-minute extended special of "Muscle Banker."
I'm already sleepy.
I don't think it's good to study while sleep-deprived.
I'll do my homework at 6AM tomorrow morning if I can wake up.
With that, GOOD NIGHT
I hope Mio-chan is doing her homework.
(Mio) April 27th.
My life! It burnt out...
I'm already a corpse...
(Principal) April 28th.
Thursday.
Starting tomorrow, I've got a three day break.
I have to work hard to come up with lots of funny jokes.
Next week's morning assembly is going to have everyone in stitches!
(Hakase) April 29th.
Hakase's great adventure!
I woke up in the morning!
I slept at night!
The end!
(Yukko) April 30th.
I forgot...
about the flower viewing...
Mogami river.
Yukko.