One, two, three, four!
It's about time for a break, Katsuragi-san.
Oh, okay...!
Got it!
Lately, you've been listening to what I say.
Oh, come on...
You're making me sound like a spoiled brat...
There are people who won't do something unless they're told to, but...
I've never seen someone who won't take a break unless they're told to.
Uh, uh...
In fact, there are times when I tell you to rest, and you still don't.
Hahaha...
Don't try to laugh it off. Honestly...
But more importantly, Senpai!
What's our next goal?!
Well, if we're setting the next goal, it would probably be 'H.I.F.', but—
Given the current situation, it's unlikely we'll qualify.
Yeah, you're right...
However, there is a solid foundation for you to soar, Katsuragi-san.
A foundation...?
An event for the next generation of idols... It's perfect for you, Katsuragi-san.
Wow, that sounds incredible!
I definitely want to participate, Senpai!
I'll spread my wings there!
The time has finally come.
The time has come for our Gokugetsu Academy to crush Hatsuboshi Academy!
Shion, you understand why you've been called here, right?
So I just need to massacre the students of Hatsuboshi Academy, is that it?
...Should we call on Gekka-neesama?
No, as long as a Prima Stella doesn't show up,
There's no need to call Gekka back.
Besides...
I've already put a plan in place to crush them.
Shion.
We'll show those incompetents the true power of Gokugetsu Academy.
Got it?
Understood, Chairman.
I'll take care of those foolish Hatsuboshi students myself.
"The Next Idol Audition..."
That's my next goal, isn't it?
That's right, Katsuragi-san. To achieve that goal, you need to――
I need to grow my fanbase...
That's right, isn't it?
That's how it is.
My fans...
I just can't picture it...
I'm sure there will be lots of amazing idols competing, right...?
Will there be anyone cheering for me among them...?
At the very least, there's one person right in front of you.
Senpai...
Thank you.
I've gained a little bit of courage.
'N.I.A.' is a nationwide competition.
Katsuragi-san, you're going to be in the spotlight more than ever before.
Yeah, that's true...
I'm nervous...
Thanks to your lessons, you're able to sing in front of an audience, Katsuragi-san.
That said, overcoming something you're not good at isn't so easy.
Y-yes...
Just imagining it makes my stomach hurt...
Let's take it step by step. This competition is the perfect opportunity for that.
I'll do my best...!
...But what should I do to win over the fans?
We have various activities planned, but I'll handle the scheduling.
As always, just keep giving it your all, Katsuragi-san.
Is that really enough...?
Yes. I'm sure that's the best way.
Well, I'm not really sure, but...
I trust your words, Senpai.
I'm really good at giving it my all...!
...That's all I can do, though.
It's okay. You're definitely growing, Katsuragi-san.
Step by step, steadily. Now you can hold your own against other idols.
...Senpai.
Hehe... I'm so happy.
You have a great expression, Katsuragi-san.
Eek...!?
S-Senpai...!?
Can I post this photo on social media? I want people to get to know you, Katsuragi-san.
I don't mind, but...
You didn't have to take it so suddenly...
So, is it okay if I take the photo?
Oh, this is so embarrassing...
But still...
If it means gaining more fans...!
That's the spirit. Gaining fans is the first step to becoming an idol.
I'll do my best to help share your charm with as many people as possible.
Thank you... I'll do my best!
Let's rise to the top together.
Yes...!
Look, Katsuragi-san. The number of votes has increased since yesterday.
Really...?
I can hardly believe it...
I wonder why they became my fans...
There are a lot of different opinions out there. But the most common one is—
Seeing you work so hard is really inspiring.
I feel the same way. I always feel better watching you.
Hehe... I'm so happy...
(...The number of votes for Katsuragi-san are gradually increasing.)
(However, it's true that the number is still lower compared to other idols.)
Senpai...?
Is something wrong?
...No, it's nothing.
(For now, I'll keep quiet. What Katsuragi-san needs is confidence.)
Can I take a guess at what you're thinking, Senpai?
Huh...?
If you're talking about the vote counts for other idols,
You can tell just by looking at the rankings.
Of course, I know that my position is low.
I see.
Even so, I...
I'm more happy than frustrated.
It might be fewer compared to other idols, but...
Even so,
So many people have come to like me.
They wanted to support someone like me...
That's what they thought.
That's why...
I'm really happy.
For you, Katsuragi-san, fans aren't just numbers, are they?
...They aren't, you know?
Each and every one of them is important to me.
Well, of course, having more fans would be great.
(...As a professional, I tend to focus on numbers, but I really need to reflect on that.)
Katsuragi-san, you're doing great just as you are. Let's keep moving forward with your activities.
Yes...!
We're performing at an event today. We were lucky that a spot opened up.
Wow, there are so many people here...
This time, a lot of top idols from 'N.I.A' will be performing.
There are so many famous people here...
Is it really okay for me to be here...?
It's true that the other performers are all top-tier idols compared to you, Katsuragi-san, but...
It's an opportunity for many people to get to know you.
I-I understand...!
Do your best. I'm cheering for you.
I completely messed up...
I wonder if Senpai is disappointed in me...
Hey, you over there.
Huh...?
May I ask for your name?
I'm... Lilja Katsuragi.
...Katsuragi.
I've never heard of you.
The number of followers is...
What is this?
Isn't it too few?
...I'm genuinely curious, though.
Why are you even here?
I'm... I'm sorry...
You should know your place.
You were holding us back today, weren't you?
Are you even aware of it?
...Yes.
I'm sorry...
...Even after all that, you can't muster a single complaint, can you?
...I was the one holding everyone back.
That's the truth.
So... I'm sorry.
I'll make sure it doesn't happen again next time.
This is just some friendly advice—
You don't have any talent.
I suggest you quit while you can.
I know that too.
Even so, I...
I've decided to become an idol.
...I don't like that look in your eyes.
Oh, by the way—
So, you have a producer backing you too, huh?
Yes!
He's a really kind person.
He really doesn't have an eye for talent, does he?
Just like you—no talent.
...What?
And he doesn't even notice it.
Maybe he's not that bright too, huh?
Wha...
...Take that back, please.
I can't forgive you for badmouthing Senpai.
Oh, really?
I was just stating the facts.
Do you really have a reason to be angry?
That's not true.
So... please take it back.
Heh heh heh...
Are you frustrated?
Well, this is pointless.
There's a world of difference between your level and mine.
Know your place.
Well then.
(...I couldn't say anything.)
(It doesn't matter what I say right now.)
(I can't prove it.)
(Because I don't have any talent...)
(I thought it didn't matter what anyone said.)
(But...)
(I can't stand it when Senpai is insulted because of me...)
(Unforgivable)
If that's the case...
I can't stay like this.
No... no, that's not it.
Sharper, smoother...
...Katsuragi-san.
...Yes?
What is it?
Is there something on your mind?
...No, not really?
There's really nothing in particular...
If you say so. I just hope that's really the case...
Um...
I'll continue with the lesson.
You seem out of breath. How about we take a little break?
No...
I'm fine...!
I can still keep going!
Please don't push yourself too hard.
I'm almost there.
I feel like I'm on the verge of something...!
(What is this feeling...? It's not just about being motivated...)
(It's like there's an intense, almost overwhelming energy...)
...Senpai.
I...
I was mistaken.
Mistaken...?
Until now...
Even if I lost to other idols,
Somewhere in my heart, I always thought this:
"It can't be helped."
Everyone else is more amazing than me.
But that's not how it should be.
With that kind of mindset...
There's no way I can win 'N.I.A.'
...You're right about that.
...Senpai.
I will win.
I'll definitely pass the next audition.
...Yes, that's the spirit. I'm rooting for you.
Yes!
(Something definitely happened.)
...Yeah, just like that.
There weren't any major mistakes...
Alright.
Let's check the choreography and go through it one more time!
That's enough, Katsuragi-san.
Huh, Senpai...?
Why are you here...?
That's my line. Didn't I tell you we're done for today?
But... just a little longer...!
Katsuragi-san, I've told you before. Overworking yourself isn't good.
What's going on? Katsuragi-san seems to be in a rush about something.
I...
I don't want to say.
...Katsuragi-san.
I'm sorry...
Excuse me.
(It seems like she'll continue practicing when no one's watching.)
(No matter what happened, she's in a precarious state right now.)
Hmm.
Did you come to ask me?
Yes, I thought you might know something, Shiun.
...Sorry, I want to help, but I don't know either.
Of course, I've noticed that Lilja's been acting a bit strange lately, but....
I told her to take a break today, but do you know where Katsuragi-san is?
Probably practicing somewhere, I guess.
And probably making sure no one knows.
...the movie of Lilja's favorite anime just came out.
It was just released yesterday.
I invited her, but...
She turned me down.
She's not willing to talk to either you or me, huh...
Shiun-san...
I couldn't stop her.
...Please, Producer.
Please stop Lilja.
The way she is now...
It's scary to watch.
She reminds me a lot of how I was before I got injured.
(Today's a day off...)
(But I can't afford to take a break right now.)
(I, who lacks talent,)
(To surpass the other idols—)
(I have to push myself harder than them.)
Katsuragi-san, I've told you before. Overworking yourself isn't good.
(If it means proving myself—)
(I don't care if my body breaks down)
(...I'm sorry, Senpai)
...Lilja?
Oh, good morning, Sumika-chan.
Good morning.
Where are you going so early in the morning?
...I'm just going for a little walk.
Oh, really?
Have a good time.
I'm still sleepy, so I'm going to sleep a little longer...
Alright, I'm heading out.
...So sleepy...
...Huh?
Wait, hold on, is she going for a walk?
Wasn't today supposed to be her complete rest day...?
No way...!
Huh?
My throat...
(Something's wrong...)
(My vision is getting blurry.)
(I can't... I need to focus more...)
Shiun-san, how's it going over there?
I'm looking everywhere I can think of, but...
I can't find her anywhere.
In that case, could she be in the practice room...?
Katsuragi-san!?
Oh, Senpai...
It looks like you've twisted your ankle. I'll call the nurse!
It looks like you've sprained your ankle.
It doesn't seem like there's any bone damage, but you should rest for a week.
Oh, no...
Alright, I'll leave you for now. Please make sure to come back to the nurse's office for a follow-up.
...Katsuragi-san. I told you today was a rest day, didn't I?
Yeah...
I'm sorry for not listening to you.
I'm sorry for being disobedient.
Even so, I just can't help but...!
Please tell me what happened.
But...
This is your punishment for breaking the rules. Please tell me.
She spoke badly about you, Senpai.
Me...?
She said you don't have an eye for talent, Senpai.
She said you don't have talent, just like me.
She went that far...!
Even after hearing all that...
—I couldn't talk back!
The reason She said that about you was because I'm not skilled enough.
If I were a more amazing idol, no one would ever say any thing like that.
So I need to show her!
That the idol you found can get real results!
As long as we can smile in the end, that's all that matters.
...Huh?
No matter how much we're ridiculed along the way, it doesn't matter.
...Even though it's my fault...?
I'm the one who made the choice. It's not your fault, Katsuragi-san.
But, still...
There are no shortcuts on the path to becoming an idol.
Pushing yourself too hard won't get you there any faster.
Yeah...
Overexerting yourself somewhere along the way can actually end up being a detour.
Like now, right...?
Your ability to give it your all is one of your greatest strengths, Katsuragi-san.
But seeing you push yourself too hard like this... it's a bit worrying.
Senpai...
I'm relieved it's not a serious injury.
It's disheartening to see my guidance being ignored like this...
Ah...
I believe that you can become a top idol, Katsuragi-san.
So, Katsuragi-san, I want you to trust your Producer—trust me.
I'm sorry...
I didn't consider your feelings...
I'll prove myself to be a producer worthy of a top idol.
I'll make sure no one ever says I lack vision or talent.
…I believe you, Senpai.
And your words.
Let's rise together.
We'll be the ones laughing in the end.
...Yes!
Lilja!?
Sumika-chan...
Oh, your foot... are you okay!?
It's just a sprain.
I think it'll heal in about a week.
Oh, I see...
I'm so relieved...
It's not a serious injury.
Um...
I'm sorry, okay?
It's not about being sorry!
You're always pushing yourself too hard!
I'm really sorry...
Overworking yourself isn't good.
Didn't the Producer tell you that?
Yeah...
I just got scolded...
...Lilja.
If this were a serious injury,
You wouldn't be able to move for a while.
In fact,
Your dream... it might not come true, you know?
Sumika-chan...
I'm really sorry.
I... didn't understand anything at all.
But it's okay now.
I'll stop pushing myself too hard on my own.
Because I trust Senpai.
Oh, Senpai?
What's going on?
I came to check if you're really taking a break, Katsuragi-san.
You don't have to be so suspicious...
I'm really just relaxing at the dorm.
I'm worried... I'm concerned you might be overdoing it again.
I've learned my lesson...!
Oh, hey, Senpai.
If you'd like, please have some of this.
Oh, is this... a cream puff?
Well, I didn't have much else to do...
I was just making some sweets.
Thank you, I'll gladly enjoy it.
How's your leg doing?
Well, running and jumping are still a bit difficult for me...
But I can walk normally now.
That's good to hear.
For now, make sure to rest properly, and then we'll start fresh again.
Yes...!
...But still,
It's hard not being able to do anything...
While I'm just sitting here, everyone else is working hard...
...Katsuragi-san, could you take a look at this for a moment?
...What is it?
Is it true you got injured? Please take it easy and rest up!
I love seeing you work hard, Katsuragi-san. But please be careful not to overdo it.
Please take it easy for now. Once you're better, show us your energetic self again.
We love you! We'll be waiting for you!
We're always cheering for you. Please take care of yourself.
This is...
These are words of encouragement from your fans.
Are these from my fans...?
That's right. Everyone is eagerly waiting for your comeback, Katsuragi-san.
They're looking forward to the day they can see you again, Katsuragi-san.
I'm so happy.
To have them support someone like me...
Thank you.
Once you get better, get back on stage, and express your gratitude to them.
One week later.
Katsuragi-san, are you all set and ready to go?
Yes...!
Just to be safe, how's your ankle doing?
I'm all set...!
Then there's nothing to worry about.
Please give your fans a good show.
Yes...!
I'm giving it everything I've got right now...!
Senpai...!
I... I did it...!
Congratulations on passing! That was an amazing performance.
Somehow...
I feel like I was able to perform beyond my usual self...
I'm sure... it's thanks to all the fans.
It's all thanks to the support I received.
...And of course, you too, Senpai.
You really know how to turn your fans' support into your own strength, don't you, Katsuragi-san?
...Yes.
Today, I really felt like everyone gave me their strength.
But we can't just sit back and celebrate.
Now that you've passed the audition, the next step is the live performance.
Yeah, you're right...
I'm starting to feel nervous about the performance...
You were able to show your strength during the special audition, so you'll be fine.
Since you've gained strength from your fans' support, make sure to express your gratitude to them.
...My gratitude...
The people who supported you, are waiting, Katsuragi-san.
Yes!
I'll give everyone the best performance I can right now...!
Yes, because that's the greatest way to repay your fans.
I'll do my best...!
Here I go!
Welcome back, Katsuragi-san.
Oh, Senpai...
I'm back.
That was an amazing performance.
I'm really... exhausted, but
I gave it my all.
After the show ended,
I thanked everyone.
I told them, "Thanks for cheering me on."
Then, even more thank-yous came pouring in...
I was surprised.
They did that because of your performance, Katsuragi-san.
Hehe, I'm so glad...
Oh, you're still here.
Oh, from back then...!
(Is that a Gokugetsu Academy uniform...?)
I can't believe you haven't given up yet.
Clinging to something so pathetic...
...Because being stubborn is my best trait.
Those eyes...
I still don't like it.
Where does that confidence even come from?
Seriously, from just that kind of performance?
This confidence was given to me by Senpai and all my friends
You don't get it, do you?
All that effort is pointless.
It's not pointless at all.
Oh, really?
I find that hard to believe...
Do you really think that if you don't give up, your dreams will come true?
It's not that I necessarily believe it will come true...
Then why do you think it's not pointless?
Because I've decided to keep running until my dreams come true.
Katsuragi-san...
...It makes my skin crawl.
All your fairytale lines.
I won't hesitate anymore.
I won't be swayed by your words anymore.
...you're just stubborn.
You don't have a shred of talent as an idol.
Hey, Producer.
Why did you choose this?
You really have no eye for talent, do you?
It's alright, Katsuragi-san. Didn't I tell you?
As long as we can smile in the end, that's all that matters.
...Yes.
I'll become a top idol!
What are you suddenly talking about...?
No matter how many years it takes,
Someday... I'll become a top idol.
I'll prove it.
The idol that Senpai chose can truly shine!
...This girl...
That being the case, please leave.
Hmph...
I understand perfectly.
Neither of you have any talent.
I won't tolerate any more insults towards Katsuragi-san.
Insults?
It's just a fact...
Fine, have it your way.
Next time we meet,
I'll show you how reality really is.
She's finally gone.
...Yes.
Um, Senpai.
Are we participating in 'FINALE' next?
Yes, I'm sure she'll be there too.
First-year student at Gokugetsu Academy, Shion Shirakusa.
Regardless of her true nature, her talent and popularity are the real deal. She's a formidable opponent.
Even so...
I don't want to lose to someone who's always looking down on others.
Katsuragi-san, the audition we're participating in is—
"FINALE."
That person—
Shirakusa-san is participating too, right?
It seems so. She's rumored to be the favorite this time.
...Actually, I watched a video of Shirakusa-san's live performance.
She was really good.
Both her singing and dancing.
She's far beyond someone like me...
...I really don't like her.
But I do respect her skills.
I think my chances of winning are quite low.
But still, that doesn't mean...
That doesn't mean we should give up, right?
Yes...!
Katsuragi-san, just do what you always do.
Can I really win by just being myself?
It's true, Shirakusa-san is a formidable opponent.
Still, there are areas where you're better.
Really...?
You understand your weaknesses. You know where you fall short.
That's why you work harder than anyone else. Sometimes, you even overdo it.
Is that the one thing where I'm better than her...?
Yes.
Katsuragi-san's "normal" is anything but ordinary.
I've come to realize something again. You're weak. And that's precisely why you're stronger than anyone else.
...Thank you so much.
I'm starting to feel a little more confident.
I'll do my very best...!
Katsuragi-san, you won.
...What?
I... won...?
Yes. Is it hard to believe?
You beat Shirakusa-san and won the whole thing, Katsuragi-san.
Um, well...
Of course, I intended to win, but...
Why... was I able to win?
Well, that's because...
It was just a fluke.
...Shirakusa-san.
No... it wasn't even a fluke.
The judges were just blind to the truth.
It's obvious that I'm the more talented one.
I refuse to accept this result...!
Your voice is shaking, Shirakusa-san.
W-What are you...!?
...It's true, I do think my skills are inferior to yours.
Isn't that right?
Then why don't you just withdraw right now!
If you do that, then—
—But in the end, I was the one who won.
Y-you...!
...So, please take back what you said.
What you said about Senpai.
I'm not wrong...!
You guys don't have any talent!
...Why do you have to go that far?
It's alright, Katsuragi-san. There's no need for her to take back what she said.
You've already proved yourself.
...You!!
Hey, hey, what's that all about?
Is there some kind of argument? Didn't one of them pass?
I will never forgive those incompetents.
I will definitely clear this humiliation...!!
She doesn't trust anyone. She just has the skills.
I don't believe a performance from someone who doesn't open their heart can truly reach anyone else's.
...Did my performance really reach their hearts?
Even you believed in Shirakusa-san. You thought, "That girl is strong."
That's why you kept working so hard. You always gave it her all.
Yes, it is.
Because that's a given.
If I don't recognize the strength of others, and my own weaknesses, I can't even get to the starting line.
That's what makes you so appealing, Katsuragi-san.
Even if your skills were rough, your performance must have moved the judges.
...Is that so?
You know, it's okay to be happier about this, right?
...Even though I'm the one who passed.
It's true that I'm not as skilled yet.
...So, the next time we meet,
I'll become strong enough to win on my own merits...!
...That's just like you, Katsuragi-san.
...Senpai.
Did you watch me?
Of course, I was watching.
Did I do okay?
Yes. It was an amazing performance.
Well, actually...
I was so focused that I don't really remember much about the performance.
...Before I knew it, I was here.
You really gave it your all.
...Yes.
I think I really gave it my all.
All I remember was how much fun it was, and one more thing...
...the expressions on the faces of the people who came to the venue.
Before it started, I was nervous and anxious...
I had a stomachache, but...
Standing on stage,
Seeing everyone's faces helped me calm down a bit.
...Why?
I realized something.
The people here were cheering for me.
If I couldn't live up to those expectations...
Then I couldn't become the idol I admired back then.
That's what I thought...
After that, I was just desperate to give it my all.
On stage, you were already a remarkable idol.
Oh, thank you.
Senpai, I...
I'll become a top idol!
I'll keep giving it my all!
That's the spirit. Would you like to review the video of the performance?
Oh...!?
I'd love to see it...!
Would you join me for a review session?
Of course, I'll join you.
Thank you so much.
From now on, and forever...
Until the day I can smile at the end.
Thank you so much, Senpai!
Let's reflect on today's production.
Katsuragi-san never stopped moving forward. That's why she soared so high this time.
However, there's a certain risk in her progress. ...It's my fault that she stumbled.
It's my job to guide her. I told her to believe.
Words carry responsibility. I, too, must prove myself.
To be a producer worthy of a future top idol.
The next step is... 'H.I.F.'.